checkcallernumber.com 2018-09-11

# Phone Lookup | Reverse Cellphone Call | Area Code lookup | Check Caller Number

#### Your Consent

By using our Website, you consent to our online Privacy Policy.

CheckCallerNumber.com may revise this Privacy Policy at any time without further notice by posting revised Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website after any such changes constitutes your acceptance of the new Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to abide any future Privacy Policy, do not use or access the Website. It is your responsibility to regularly check this page to determine if there have been changes to this Privacy Policy and to review such changes. We will post the changes to this Privacy Policy on this page and will indicate on this page the date these terms were last revised. Any revised version will be deemed applicable when published on this Website. 

#### Personal Information CheckCallerNumber.com Collects

CheckCallerNumber.com collects information about Your use of CheckCallerNumber.com. This may include information about any IP address used to access CheckCallerNumber.com and Your activity on CheckCallerNumber.com - content of your comment, name and surname under which the comment was provided, time of entering the comment. CheckCallerNumber.com uses cookies, or small text files stored on Your computer, to store data about Your visits. 

Please be informed that you have the right to access your personal data, the right to request rectification of incorrect, incomplete and inaccurate personal data and other data subject's rights established in applicable data protection laws. Please refer to Contact Page in order to implement your rights. 

#### Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers' hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. 

#### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our Website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our Website and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

#### Third party vendors

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our Website or other websites. Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet. 

#### Children's Privacy

CheckCallerNumber.com is not intended for children under the age of 18 and we do not knowingly collect any Personal Information from such children. Children under the age of 18 should not use CheckCallerNumber.com or our online services at any time, unless applicable laws allow using such service. If You are aware that CheckCallerNumber.com has collected Personal Information from someone under the age of 18 and applicable laws do not allow such collection, please alert CheckCallerNumber.com at Contact Page and the information will be removed from our system as soon as is reasonably possible. 

#### Removing your Personal Information from CheckCallerNumber.com

You may remove your information from the CheckCallerNumber.com phone directory, please contact us via Contact Page, your information will be removed from our system as soon as is reasonably possible, however, no longer than 14 working days. For any suggestions and comments regarding CheckCallerNumber.com or our Privacy Policy, please contact us via Contact Page. If you feel this Website does not comply with any of the above stated Privacy Policy terms or if you have any questions you can Contact Us. 

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page.
